{
  "shortDescription": "Test your manga knowledge with this quiz.",
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Who is the ninja?",
      "answers": ["Naruto", "Goku", "Luffy"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Futur Pirate King?",
      "answers": ["Luffy", "Zoro", "Nami"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Death Note owner?",
      "answers": ["Light", "L", "Ryuk"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Dragon Balls main caracter?",
      "answers": ["Goku", "Vegeta", "Bulma"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Alchemist main caracter??",
      "answers": ["Edward", "Alphonse", "Mustang"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Soul Reaper main caracter??",
      "answers": ["Ichigo", "Renji", "Orihime"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Titan slayer main caracter??",
      "answers": ["Eren", "Mikasa", "Levi"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Demon Slayer main caracter??",
      "answers": ["Tanjiro", "Nezuko", "Zenitsu"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Future Diary main caracter??",
      "answers": ["Yuno", "Yuki", "Akise"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Alchemy symbol?",
      "answers": ["Circle", "Star", "Cube"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Hero school?",
      "answers": ["UA", "SA", "TA"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Ghoul city?",
      "answers": ["Tokyo", "Kyoto", "Osaka"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Hunter x Hunter main caracter?",
      "answers": ["Gon", "Killua", "Kurapika"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Blue Exorcist?",
      "answers": ["Rin", "Yukio", "Shura"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "SAO game?",
      "answers": ["Kirito", "Asuna", "Sinon"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Detective Conan?",
      "answers": ["Conan", "Ran", "Kogoro"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Fire user?",
      "answers": ["Natsu", "Gray", "Erza"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Cursed fingers?",
      "answers": ["Yuji", "Megumi", "Nobara"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Gintama weapon?",
      "answers": ["Sword", "Gun", "Staff"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Black Clover?",
      "answers": ["Asta", "Yuno", "Noelle"],
      "correctAnswerIndex": 0
    }
  ]
}
